http://www.premierleague.com/premier-league-policies

Close Advert
Premier League Policies
The Premier League respects and protects the data and privacy of the fans, players, suppliers, contractors and other individuals who we come into contact with in order to carry out our work.  The Premier League is committed to being open with individuals about how we use their information and who we give it to and will comply with all applicable data protection regulations. Further information on what data we collect, why we collect it and what we do with it can be found in our privacy policies below:
Premier League Privacy Policy - This policy explains how the Premier League uses personal data when people access the Premier League websites; use the Premier League's official app; play Fantasy Premier League; contact the Fanzone; engage with the Premier League (or we engage with their content) on social media platforms; and/or when they otherwise interact or communicate with the Premier League.
Premier League Player and Related Persons Privacy Policy - This policy explains how the Premier League uses personal data provided by, or received in respect of, players and academy players as well as persons associated with such players and the Premier League including, player family members, match officials, agents, managers, trialists, coaches, scouts, club staff, directors (including shadow directors and club owners) and the personnel of current and prospective broadcast partners and other official licensees.
Premier League Safeguarding Privacy Policy – This policy explains how the Premier League uses personal data in relation to the safeguarding of children and adults at risk.
Premier League Enforcement Privacy Policy – This policy explains how the Premier League collects and uses personal data as part of its efforts to protect and enforce its intellectual property rights.
Cookies on PremierLeague.com
The Premier League website employs cookies to improve your user experience. We have updated our cookie policy to reflect changes in the law on cookies and tracking technologies used on websites. If you continue on this website, you will be providing your consent to our use of cookies.
Find out more
I accept cookies from this site
